A Guide to the China Medical Board, Inc. records, RG 1 FA065
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Scholarships (A-G) (Box 141, Folder 1023)
  Anhwei Fund, 1928 (Greene); Chu Ming-liang Memorial Fund, 1941; Thomas Cochrane Fund, 1923-1927, 1931-1934 (Cochrane, Thomas; Comptroller; Director; Greene; Hawkins, F. H.; Houghton; Lenwood, Frank); Entrance Fund, 1926-1928, 1931 (Comptroller; Gee; Greene; Rockefeller, John D. Jr.); Anna Fuller Fund, 1949-1950 (Cooper, James W.; Townshend, Raynham); Greene Fund, 1935-1936
- Scholarships - Harvard Medical School in China, 1925-1951, 1963 (Box 141, Folder 1024)
  Adams, Charles F.; Berry, George P.; Claflin, William H.; Dashiell; Debevoise; Greene; Houghton; Hunnewell, F. W.; Lowell, Abbott L.; Lyman-Grew Fund; Moore, Edward C.; Resident Director; Robinson, Edward; Shattuck, Henry L.; Wood, Henry A.
- Scholarships (H-T) (Box 142, Folder 1025)
  Holders, 1924-1940: Director; Harvard Medical School in China; Resident Director; Rockefeller, J. D. Jr.; Thomas Cochrane Fund (Chen, Chih-chien; Cochrane, Thomas; Director; Greene; Houghton; Huang, Kuo-an; Wang, Mei-ying)
  Nursing School, 1921-1927 (Houghton; Ingram)
  Nursing School Alumnae Memorial Fund, 1948-1949 (Comptroller; Hsy, Yu-hung; Nieh, Y. C.) Ting Fund, 1947
  Trustees, 1922-1923 (Armitage, J. Auriol; Barton, James L.; Flexner, Simon; Goodrich; Hogg, James S.; Houghton; Mott, J. A.; North, Frank M.; Reid, J. Christie; Rockefeller, J. D. Jr.; Vincent; Welch, William H.)
- Sch-Sea (Box 142, Folder 1026)
  Schools for Children of Staff, 1917-1918, 1922 (Howard, Harvey J.); Schweinitz, George E. de, 1921-1922; Scwentker, Victor, 1950-1951; Seal (of the University), 1924 (Director)
  Items of special note in this folder include a bulletin for North China American School, Tungchou, Chihli (1917-1918), found under the mark-up School for Children of Staff.
- Secretaries (B-L) (Box 142, Folder 1027)
  Barnes, Bessie Pearl, 1930; Barton, Olive, 1931; Bourne, Florence G. K., 1921, 1925; Breed, Eleanor D., 1931, 1934; Brunnert, Mary, 1925-1926; Carroll, Beatrice, 1941, 1949, 1971; Cates, Catherine B., 1923, 1926; Chang, I-shao, 1925; Chang, Kuo-liang, 1927; Chang, Pei-ju, 1929, 1951, 1954; Chang, Shu-sheng, 1925-1926; Chen, James S., 1925-1927, 1935-1935, 1945-1946; Chen, Pao-kun, 1927, 1949; Chiang, I-hung, 1927, 1946; Chien, Archibald P., 1931, 1946-1947, 1951; Chun, Feng-shan, 1927; Chung, Heng-hsu, 1929; Clifford, May, 1926; Dawley, Mary E., 1926; Dixon, Margarete, 1924, 1963; Don, Esta, 1924-1925; Eccles, Olive, 1926; Estcourt, Doris, 1922-1923; Ettinger, Ingelborg H., 1930-1932; Farina, Julie A., 1924; Farmer, Dora, 1926-1927; Faung, Zoong-hway, 1927-1929, 1933; Feng, Ta-wei (David), 1927; Figourousky, Claudia, 1931; Gordon, J. Dorothy, 1919, 1921; Gordon, Sara E., 1925; Grey, Ramona, 1924; Halsey, M. S., 1924; Han, Baytoung (Violet), 1927; Hempel, Olga M., 1926; Hill, P., 1935; Hot Kuen-nien, 1927; Hodgson, Blanche, 1923-1925; Hoffman, Doris L., 1933; Homan, Resi, 1924-1925, 1929; Hyde, Minnie, 1924; Kemp, Dorothy, 1932, 1935; King, Edna M., 1935, 1963; Krenz, Julia S., 1933-1935; Kuo, Gladys, 1929; Kuo, Tulda, 1930; Lamkert, Olga, 1924; Lawrence, Anne, 1924; Leitch, Mary, 1926; Lit Chih-chieh, 1922, 1926; Liu, Chen, 1924 Leuhrs, Marta E., 1927; Luther, Jean, 1926
- Secretaries (M-S) (Box 142, Folder 1028)
  MacTavish, Janet, 1929; March, Helen, 1926-1929; Mason, Elizabeth, 1921-1923; McCoy, Mary V., 1925; McKillop, Marjorie L., 1925-1927; Mears, Helen, 1925-1926; Munroe, Elizabeth, 1921-1925; Oates, Nevitt, 1925; Parkhurst, Anne, 1921, 1925; Pearce, Emily C., 1923-1924; Peers, Adeline C., 1924-1927, 1931, 1951; Penne, John L., 1927, 1935; Plath, Minnie, 1925-1927; Popoff, Alexandra, 1924; Price, Ruth A., 1929, 1933-1935, 1941, 1956-1958; Raphaelson, Rayna, 1924; Robson, May G., 1932-1933; Russell, Helen., 1920-1922, 1971; Salter, Ruth, 1924-1925; Scott, Selma, 1925-1927; Searight, Jeannette, 1924, 1927; Shao, Caroline M., 1926-1927; Shao, Shang-hsien, 1927; Shoolingin, V., 1933; Smith, Clara, 1924; Smith, Marjorie, 1924-1925; Smith, R. E., 1924; Speshneff, Galia N., 1927-1930, 1936-1937, 1945; Sternberg, Alix U., 1924-1929, 1969; Stimpson, 1924; Stolk, Frederika C., 1929
- Secretaries (T-W) (Box 142, Folder 1029)
  Thuermer, Emilie, 1943-1945, 1960-1966; Thunder, Helen, 1944, 1950-1962; Tien, Chi-sheng, 1931; Tung, Fu-min, 1927; Tung, Fu-ming, 1931; Walker, Mildred (see Walker); Wats, G., 1926; Wei, Tsze-chun, 1926-1927; Whitten, Edith, 1924; Wingfield, B., 1932; Woodcock, Ida M., 1924, 1927, 1930, 1953; Worthington, Alberta, undated.
- Sh-Sk (Box 142, Folder 1030)
  Shanghai Child Welfare Clinic, 1934 (Chiang, C. C.); Shanghai Commercial and Savings Bank, 1945-1946 (Balfour); Shanghai Medical Centre, 1945-1946 (Brown, Robert E.); Shanghai Medical Congress, 1923; Shanghai Medical School, 1919, 1930 (see also Rockefeller Foundation - Misc. Photographs) (Greene); Shanghai Medical School Minutes, 1919-1921; Shangtung Christian University 1931 (Shilds); Shek, John L., 1950; Shen, Chite, 1928-1929; Shen, Shu-chu, 1946-1947; Shen, Tan-hua, 1932; Shenchon, Eleanor, 1929-1933; Shields, R. T., 1944-1945; Sia, Fu-tsin (Anna), 1927-1928; Sio, Sing-ming, 1948; Sigler, W. Warren, 1923, 1926-1929, 1944; Silvert, Meyer, 1945; Skrovseth, Signe, 1946
- Sm-Sn (Box 142, Folder 1031)
  Smithsonian Institute - Hrdlicka, Ales, 1919-1920, 1924, 1939; Smyly, William, 1921-1922; Snell, 1947; Snite, Fred, 1937, 1954
- Social Service, 1919-1930, 1935, 1939 (Box 142, Folder 1032)
  Cannon, Ida M.; Director; Greene; Holland, W. L.; Houghton; Pearce, R. M.; Pruitt, Ida; Swartz, Philip A.
- Social Service (Ch-Pa) (Box 142, Folder 1033)
  Chang, Chung-tang, 1934, 1948-1950; Chao, Hsi-fan, 1934; Chen, Gertrude, 1932; Chen, Ke-chun, 1925-1926; Chen, (Wei-kin) Ruth, 1933, 1946 ;Cheng, K. W. C., 1930; Chi, Chih-ting (Florence), 1934; Chien, Chieh-hua (Pearl), 1935, 1941, 1944-1949; Chou, Li-chiu, 1927, 1932-1935; Chu, Shi (Grace), 1929; Chung, Hsien-ying, 1929; Han, Tu, 1934; Hsu, En-hsi, 1934; Hsu, Lang-kuang (Francis), 1934; Huang, Chen-chiu, 1933; Ingram, Isabel M., 1922-1927; Jao, Yu-ai, 1933; Kao, Chun-che, 1930; Kao, Sau-mei, 1930; Lee, En-fu, 1928; Li, Chang Chun-ying, 1933; Li, Fu-man, 1930; Li, Kuan, 1933; Li, Shan-chen, 1930, 1935; Li, Yen-feng (Nellie Lee), 1934; Liang, Phebe, 1954, 1960, 1963; Lin, (Shu-yin) Julia, 1930-1935; Ling, Lien-chen, 1928; Liu, Tsi-chu, 1933; New, (Feng-ying) Rose P., 1925; Newell, Mary H., 1928; Nieh, Yu-chin (Miriam), 1931-1932; Pai, Tuan, 1930
- Social Service - Pruitt, Ida, 1919-1939, 1945-1948, 1954-1956, 1960, 1964 (Box 143, Folder 1034)
- Social Service (R-Z) (Box 143, Folder 1035)
  Rabinowitz, Annette, 1933-1940; She, Hui-chen, 1932; Sung, Ssu-ming, 1929, 1933; Tao, Ling, 1930, 1933; Tien, Kuei-luan, 1933; Ting, Tsung, 1934; Tsao Ching-wu, 1932; Tsou, George Y., 1928, 1937; Tsu, Caroline, 1931; Wang, Jeanie, 1928; Wang, Tze-ming, 1929, 1934; Yu, Ju-chi, 1926, 1929-1933, 1939, 1947; Zien, Zang-pung, 1928-1930
- Soc-Sou (Box 143, Folder 1036)
  Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1922-1923, 1949-1950 (Comptroller; Houghton; Jackson, Holmes; McLean, Franklin C.); Society for the Propagation of the Gospel in Foreign Parts, 1924-1929, 1944 (Weir, H. H.); Soo, T. L., 1948; Soong, Aloy P., 1914-1920; Soong, Ts-vung, 1942-1945, 1971; South African Institute for Medical Research, 1949
- Southwest China, 1942-1945 (Box 143, Folder 1037)
  Forkner; Greene; Memo; Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Chairs
  Items of special note in this folder include Survey of Medical Aid Given to China by American Organizations in the War Emergency (April 1 - June 1, 1942).
- Southwest China - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) School of Nursing, 1942-1943 August (Box 143, Folder 1038)
- Southwest China - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) School of Nursing, 1943 September-1944 February (Box 143, Folder 1039)
- Southwest China - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) School of Nursing, 1944 March-October (Box 143, Folder 1040)
- Southwest China - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) School of Nursing, 1944 November-1945 (Box 143, Folder 1041)
- Southwest China - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) School of Nursing, 1946-1947 (Box 144, Folder 1042)
- Sp-Stan (Box 144, Folder 1043)
  Speed, Kellogg, 1930-1931; Squibb Institute, 1938-1941 (Greene; Harrop, George A.); Stampar, A., 1932; Stanford University, 1926-1927 (Wilbur, Ray L).
- Statistics, 1914-1915 (Box 144, Folder 1044)
- Statistics, 1920-1951 (Box 144, Folder 1045)
  Goodrich; Greene; Houghton; Macmillan; Personnel (Balfour; Greene); Resident Director; Staff - Houghton; Students - Greene
- Statistics - Alumni, 1919, 1923-1925, 1933, 1942-1946, 1950 (Box 144, Folder 1046)
  Greene; London Missionary Society - Cochrane, Thomas; Macmillan; Personnel (Tsur)
  See also Box 162, Folder 25
- Statistics - Enrollment, 1927-1932 (Box 144, Folder 1047)
- Statistics - Nurses, 1923-1938 (Box 144, Folder 1048)
- Statistics - Registration, 1922-1931 (Box 144, Folder 1049)
  Director; Greene
- Statistics - Registration, 1932-1947 (Box 144, Folder 1050)
- Step-Stif (Box 144, Folder 1051)
  Stephenson, Bird R., 1959; Stevens, F. W., 1923; Stifler, W. W., 1920-1921
  Items of special note in this folder include Suggested Changes in Administrative Organization of Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) and Proposed Constitution (1920) and Pre-Medical Education - Trip to South China (1921), both found under the mark-up Stifler.
- Stim-Stuc (Box 145, Folder 1052)
  Stimpson, Julia, 1923-1924, 1942; Stolz, Berta Helene, 1929; Stone, Robert, 1922, 1928, 1930; Storms, R. W., 1928; Strong, J. B., 1924-1925; Stuart, Leighton, 1942-1945, 1955-1956, 1962; Stuckey, E. J., 1917-1919
- Students (Box 145, Folder 1053)
  Student Association - Handbook (see Handbook); Students, 1914-1916, 1925, 1933-1934, 1939, 1941, 1946-1947 (Director; Library - Hogg); Students from the United States (Bock, Rudolf, 1929; Lum, Paul, 1934-1935; Mather, William B., 1933-1934; Smith, Malcolm B., 1947)
- Sun-Sup (Box 145, Folder 1054)
  Sun, Alfred, 1944-1946; Sun, (Ching-yun) Lucille, 1947; Sun, Pang-tsao, 1950; Sun, (Yi-hsuan) Winston, 1949; Sun, Yun-chan, 1923-1924, 1931; Sun Memorial Prize, 1933-1941; Sun Yat-sen Memorial Medical College, 1942, 1948 (Hsu, Tien-lu); Sung, Chieh, 1945-1946; Sung, Yi, 1949; Supplies, 1940-1951 (Armour and Co.; Bausch and Lomb Optical Co.; Eimer and Amend)
- Surgery, 1921-1929 (Box 145, Folder 1055)
- Surgery, 1930-1941 (Box 145, Folder 1056)
  Blalock, Alfred; Director; Firor; Greene; Handbook; Houghton; Publications - Loucks; Reichert, Frederick; Reid, Mont; Resident Director; Zinninger, M. M.
  Items of special note include a plot plan of the Surgery Department.
- Surgery - Staff (Biel-Chan) (Box 145, Folder 1057)
  Biello, Joseph A., 1929, 1962; Brackett, E. G., 1922; Branch, Joseph R. B., 1927-1929; Canright, Cyril M., 1928; Chang, Chao-hwei, 1929; Chang, Chi-cheng, 1930-1931, 1935-1940; Chang, Hsien-lin, 1933-1939, 1942-1948, 1953, 1969; Chang, Tien-min, 1941, 1946-1948; Chang, Tung-ho, 1927, 1946-1947
  Items of special note in this folder include a Report on Orthopedic Surgery (1922), found under the mark-up Surgery - Staff - Brackett; and a photograph of Tung-ho Chang (December 22, 1946), found under the mark-up Surgery - Staff - Chang, Tung-ho.
- Surgery - Staff (Chao-Char) (Box 145, Folder 1058)
  Chao, Hsueh, 1928; Chao, Pre-chuan, 1950; Chao, Yi-cheng, 1934-1939, 1949-1950, 1958, 1962; Char, (Wen-chuang) Florence, 1947-1958, 1962
- Surgery - Staff - Char, George Y., 1914-1932, 1936-1938, 1943-1952 (Box 146, Folder 1059)
- Surgery - Staff (Chen - Chu, H.H.) (Box 146, Folder 1060)
  Chen, Ching-yun, 1937-1938; Chen, Heng-I, 1933-1934, 1945; Chen, Karl, 1948-1950; Chen, Kuo-hsi, 1941, 1948; Chen, Ming-chai, 1938, 1940, 1946-1947, 1950; Cheng, Fu-ming, 1950; Chi, Chang-ken, 1928; Chia, Wei-lien, 1938; Chiang, Ju-chi, 1933; Chiang, R. Y., 1926; Chien, Swen-yu, 1927; Chin, Chen-ting (see Surgery - Staff - Wu, Ying-kai); Chinn, Alexander B., 1926-1929; Chou, (Chin-hua) Edward, 1938, 1944-1948; Chou, (Ting-shih) Thomas, 1949; Chou, Yu-teh, 1933-1934, 1945; Chow, (Peh-ling) Philip, 1930; Chu, Hung-han, 1941
- Surgery - Staff (Chu, L. C. - Cormack) (Box 146, Folder 1061)
  Chu, Lee-chung, 1922-1930; Chu, Wei-chi, 1949; Chu, Yen-nung, 1928; Chu, Yu-pi, 1936; Cormack, Robert, 1919, 1925-1927
- Surgery - Staff (Cro-Die) (Box 146, Folder 1062)
  Crowe, Harold E., 1923-1926; Cutler, Max, 1936-1937; Dieterick, F. H., 1915-1919
- Surgery - Staff (Dilley - Fan, J. H.) (Box 146, Folder 1063)
  Dilley, F. E., 1915-1927; Djang, Hsi-ming, 1936-1937; Fan, Hai-shan, 1936-1938, 1945; Fan, Kuo-sung, 1940-1941; Fan, Jih-hsien, 1935, 1942-1943, 1948
- Surgery - Staff (Fan, T. - Hsu, H.A.) (Box 146, Folder 1064)
  Fan, Tu, 1948-1949; Fan, Yueh-cheng, 1937-1938, 1946-1947; Fang, Hsieh-chih, 1934-1946; Feng, Chuan-han, 1940-1945; Feng, Chuan-I, 1949; Gibson, Douglas M.,1927; Grey, 1919; Guggs, Daniel E., 1927; Ha, Huan-wen, 1950; Heiner, Robert G., 1931; Ho, Tien-chi, 1941, 1950; Holman, Emilie F., 1927, 1950; Howe, Yu-lin, 1948-1950; Hsieh, Yu-chang, 1949-1950; Hsiung, Ju-cheng, 1937; Hsu, Chi-ho, 1935; Hsu, Hsing-an, 1933-1935, 1946-1947
- Surgery - Staff (Hsu, S. - Kwan, G. P.) (Box 146, Folder 1065)
  Hsu, Shu, 1928; Hsu, Yin-hsiang, 1933-1934; Hu, Chen, 1948-1949; Huang, Chia-ssu, 1933-1934, 1941-1945; Huang, Kuo-chun, 1948-1950; Huang, Tzu-chuan, 1947-1949, 1956-1960; Johnstone, 1917; Kao, Ching-hsing, 1940; Kao, Hsien-ming, 1950; Kimm, Hyen-taik, 1933, 1936-1939, 1945-1947, 1956-1959, 1965; Kwae, Sze-sung, 1948-1949; Kwan, G. Paul, 1931-1935
- Surgery - Staff - Kwan, Sung-tao, 1922-1972 (Box 147, Folder 1066)
- Surgery - Staff (Lee - Lin) (Box 147, Folder 1067)
  Lee, Shao-hua, 1938; Lee, Te-hsing, 1950; Lemmer, Friedrich, 1932-1934, 1941, 1950; Lew, Don G., 1922-1923; Lhamon, R. M., 1937-1938; Li, Hsuan-gus, 1928; Li, Hung-ju, 1934-1935, 1947; Li, Kung-sung, 1950; Lin, Pi-chin, 1940
- Surgery - Staff - Ling, (Chih-ming) James, 1941, 1946-1957 (Box 147, Folder 1068)
- Surgery - Staff (Liu) (Box 147, Folder 1069)
  Liu, Ching-tung, 1938, 1944-1956; Liu, Kum, 1950; Liu, Kuo-chen, 1948-1949; Liu, Shen-erh, 1932, 1937-1938, 1946-1948
- Surgery - Staff - Loucks, Harold H.
  - 1921-1928 (Box 147, Folder 1070)
  - 1929-1933 (Box 147, Folder 1071)
  - 1934-1941 (Box 147, Folder 1072)
  - 1942-1945 September (Box 147, Folder 1073)
  - 1945 October-1950 (Box 148, Folder 1074)
    Items of special note in this folder include Surgical Assembly on 20th Anniversary of Louck's Appointment and photographs of the 20th Anniversary of Louck's appointment (April 23, 1950).
- Surgery - Staff (Lu-Mel) (Box 148, Folder 1075)
  Lu, (Kwan-chuan) Morgan, 1937-1941, 1945-1958, 1969, 1972; Marshall, Leslie B., 1939, 1965; McClure, Robert B., 1935, 1938, 1957, 1960, 1964-1966; Meleney, Frank L., 1916, 1920-1925
- Surgery - Staff - Meng, Chi-mao, 1925-1932, 1936, 1940, 1945-1952 (Box 148, Folder 1076)
- Surgery - Staff (Mi-Pi) (Box 148, Folder 1077)
  Miltner, Leo J., 1930-1938, 1942, 1969; New, Way-sung, 1914-1922; Oman, Charles M., 1926; Pi, Hwa-tung, 1950
- Surgery - Staff (Reid - Shen) (Box 148, Folder 1078)
  Reid, Mont R., 1923-1931; Shen, (Ko-fei) James, 1924-1929, 1943-1947, 1958
- Surgery - Staff (Shep-So) (Box 148, Folder 1079)
  Shepard, George W., 1935-1936; Shih, Hsi-en, 1933-1939, 1945-1947, 1958, 1966; Soong, Hsien-wen, 1948-1950
- Surgery - Staff - Spies, John W., 1931-1962 (Box 148, Folder 1080)
- Surgery - Staff - Spies, John W. (Lawsuit), 1935 (Box 148, Folder 1081)
- Surgery - Staff (St-Sz) (Box 148, Folder 1082)
  Stearns, Thornton, 1916-1917, 1925-1926, 1951, 1961, 1967; Su, Ying, 1940; Szutu, (Chan) Gene, 1933, 1940-1941, 1945-1947, 1951-1955, 1961-1964
- Surgery - Staff - Taylor, Adrian S., 1914-1920 (Box 149, Folder 1083)
- Surgery - Staff - Taylor, Adrian S., 1921-1928 (Box 149, Folder 1084)
- Surgery - Staff - Taylor, Adrian S., 1929-1962 (Box 149, Folder 1085)
- Surgery - Staff (Ta-Tu) (Box 149, Folder 1086)
  Taylor, Harry B., 1923, 1927-1929, 1971; Tien, Feng-luan, 1928; Tseng, Hsien-chiu, 1940-1941, 1945, 1948-1949; Tsui, Chih-tan, 1949; Tung, Ping-chi (Sanford), 1925, 1931-1934, 1946-1947
- Surgery - Staff - Van Allen, Chester M., 1924-1929 (Box 149, Folder 1087)
  Van Allen, Lorette V.
- Surgery - Staff - Van Allen, Chester M., 1930-1935 (Box 149, Folder 1088)
- Surgery - Staff - Van Allen, Chester M., 1936 (Box 149, Folder 1089)
- Surgery - Staff - Van Allen, Chester M. (Lawsuit), 1935 (Box 149, Folder 1090)
- Surgery - Staff - Van Allen, Chester M. (Lawsuit), 1935 (Box 150, Folder 1091)
- Surgery - Staff - Van Gorder, George W., 1916, 1919-1921, 1927-1929, 1965, 1969 (Box 150, Folder 1092)
- Surgery - Staff (Wan-Web) (Box 150, Folder 1093)
  Wang, Hsing-kuo, 1928, 1932; Wang, Kai-hsi (Mark), 1932-1937, 1944-1947, 1950-1954, 1962; Wang, Shih-kuei, 1938-1941, 1953-1956; Wang, Ta-tung, 1933-1939; Webster, Jerome P., 1921-1930, 1959, 1971
- Surgery - Staff (Wed-Wu) (Box 150, Folder 1094)
  Wedekind, Gerhard, 1946-1947, 1958; Wen, Chung-chieh, 1937-1940; Wilderson, L. O., 1921-1923; Willcutts, Morton D., 1933-1935; Wong, (Sin-fook) James, 1934-1935; Wong, Wing-yuen, 1934-1937; Wu, Chih-kang, 1949-1950; Wu, (Pi-chang) Patrick; Wu, Teh-cheng, 1949-1950; Wu, Wei-jan, 1948-1950
- Surgery - Staff - Wu, Ying-kai and Chin, Chen-ting (Mrs. Y. K. Wu), 1933-1935 (Box 150, Folder 1095)
- Surgery - Staff - Wu, Ying-kai and Chin, Chen-ting (Mrs. Y. K. Wu), 1946-1950 (Box 150, Folder 1096)
- Surgery - Staff (Y-Z) (Box 150, Folder 1097)
  Yang, Ching-po, 1933-1936, 1953; Yang, Gia-liang, 1936; Yang, Ta-chun, 1924-1927, 1938; Yu, Joseph, 1929, 1940; Yu, Sung-ting, 1940-1950; Yuan, F. T., 1932; Yuan, Yin-kuang (Stephen), 1933-1935; Yui, (Hsin-en) John; Zau, Zung-dau, 1921-1929; Zinninger, Max M., 1928-1930
- Survey Commission - Minute Book - Part 1, 1936 (Box 150, Folder 1098)
- Survey Commission - Minute Book - Part 2, 1936 (Box 151, Folder 1099)
- Survey Commission - Report, 1936 (Box 151, Folder 1100)
  Items of special note in this folder include Docket - Exhibit F (1936).
- Survey Engineering - J. G. White Engineering Corp., 1945-1947 (Box 151, Folder 1101)
  Bowen, T.; Chilson, E. N.; Comptroller; Crawford, C. H.; Director; Fosdick; Loucks; Miller, D.; Parker; Sturm, W. F.; Wheeler; Williams, E.; Reopening Peking Union Medical College (PUMC); Utility Services
- Survey Engineering - J. G. White Engineering Corp. - Reports - Copy 1, 1946 (Box 151, Folder 1102)
- Survey Engineering - J. G. White Engineering Corp. - Reports - Copy 2, 1946 (Box 151, Folder 1103)
- Survey Engineering - J. G. White Engineering Corp. - Sturm, 1946-1948 (Box 151, Folder 1104)
- Sw (Box 151, Folder 1105)
  Sweden, Legation of, 1920; Swift, Harold H., 1940; Swisher, Charles P., 1925-1928; Switzerland, Legation of, 1942-1945
- Sze, S. K. A., 1926-1945 (Box 151, Folder 1106)
- Sze, S. K. A., 1946-1963 (Box 152, Folder 1107)
- Aze, Sao-ke Alfred (from Personal File), 1941-1947 (Box 152, Folder 1108)
- Sz (Box 152, Folder 1109)
  Sze, Sze-ming, 1934, 1942-1945; Szechuan Province, 1944-1945 (Chen, C. C.); Kung Li Hospital - Forkner; Provincial Medical College (Balfour; Chen, C. C.; Forkner, C. E.); Szeto, Joan Y. (Mrs. H. Frank Szeto), 1946
  Items of special note in this folder include "China's Health Problems," found under the mark-up Sze, Sze-ming.
- Ta-Te (Box 152, Folder 1110)
  Tandler, 1934; Tang, Yun-the, 1971; Tansinsin, Manuel, 1927-1927; Tao, Jung-chin, 1941-1951, 1955, 1968; Tao, Shan-ming, 1925-1926, 1936-1937, 1940; Teacher's Insurance and Annuity Association, 1927-1950 (Cameron, J.; Ferguson; Furst, C.; Hirst, E.; Hoeppli; Lim, R. K. S;. Mao, H. C.; Mattock; Pan, M. T.; Wei, Y. L.; Wu, H.; Zia, S.); Technician (Chang, En-lin, 1930; Chou, Tung-pi, 1930; Houghton, 1923; Goodrich, 1923; Ma, Yu-cheng, 1931, 1949-1950); Telephone System, 1927, 1936, 1940, 1947; Tessar, Joseph F., 1926-1932
- Th-Tr (Box 152, Folder 1111)
  Thomas Cook and Son, 1949-1951, 1957 (Hale, B. C.); Ting, Kuang-sheng, 1947-1951; Tiong, Hollington, 1942-1943; Townsend, Mollie E., 1929; Training Service, 1922-1923 (Greene; Hogg; Houghton)
- Transcripts - Class of 1924-1928 (Box 152, Folder 1112)
- Transcripts - Class of 1929-1932 (Box 152, Folder 1113)
- Transcripts - Class of 1933-1936 (Box 153, Folder 1114)
- Tr (Box 153, Folder 1115)
  Travel, 1920, 1932, 1941; Treasurer's Office, 1961, 1923-1938, 1947 (Director; Greene; Myers, F. B.; Myers, L. G.; Robinson, E.)
- Treasurer's Office - Reports, 1927-1930 (Box 153, Folder 1116)
- Treasurer's Office - Reports, 1930-1933 (Box 153, Folder 1117)
- Treasurer's Office - Reports, 1933-1940 (Box 153, Folder 1118)
- Treasurer's Office - Reports, 1940-1947 (Box 153, Folder 1119)
- Trustees, 1926-1928, 1933, 1937-1951, 1960 (Box 154, Folder 1120)
  Director; Dunlap; Memos; Recorder
- Trustees - Administrative Committee - Reports, 1935-1937 (Box 154, Folder 1121)
- Trustees - Advisory Committee, 1929-1930 (Box 154, Folder 1122)
- Trustees - Dockets, 1943-1951 (Box 154, Folder 1123)
- Trustees - Minutes, 1916-1917 (Box 154, Folder 1124)
  Trustees of Peking Union Medical College (PUMC); Executive Committee; Nominating Committee; Recorder
- Trustees - Minutes, 1917-1918, 1940 (Box 154, Folder 1125)
- Trustees - Minutes, 1944-1950 (Box 154, Folder 1126)
- Trustees (B) (Box 155, Folder 1127)
  Balfour, M. C., 1945; Ballou, E. H., 1936-1945, 1968; Barton, James L., 1927-1928; Bassett, Arthur, 1940-1942, 1947; Bennett, C. R., 1929-1932, 1939-1947; Brown, Arthur J., 1915, 1920-1922, 1927-1929
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Arthur J. Brown.
- Trustees (C-H) (Box 155, Folder 1128)
  Chang, Po-ling, 1929, 1932, 1936-1938; Chen, C. C., 1945; Chu, Keats S., 1950; Cochrane, Thomas, 1927-1928; Fang, Shisan C., 1936-1937, 1940-1941; Greene, Roger S., 1926-1931; Gregg, Alan, 1932, 1938; Hawkins, F. H., 1927; Hu, Shih, 1947
- Trustees - King, Sohtsu G., 1930-1946 (Box 155, Folder 1129)
- Trustees (Li-Th) (Box 155, Folder 1130)
  Li, Ming, 1966; Lin, Hsin-kwei, 1932-1940, 1946; Little, L. K., 1950; Liu, J. H., 1942, 1950; Lobenstine, E. C., 1930; London Missionary Society, 1928; Medical Missionary Association, London, 1928; Monroe, Paul, 1919-1931, 1935, 1947; North, Frank M., 1919-1929; Presbyterian Church, 1928; Thomas, C. F., 1950; Thompson, Norma S., 1928
- Trustees - Tsur, Y. T., 1929-1944 (Box 155, Folder 1131)
- Trustees - Tsur, Y. T., 1945-1950 (Box 155, Folder 1131A)
- Trustees (W) (Box 155, Folder 1132)
  Weir, H. H., 1927-1928; Wu, Chao-chu, 1929, 1933
- Ts-Tu (Box 156, Folder 1133)
  Tsai, Chen-shun, 1933; Tsei, Mei-teh, 1961; Tsen, T. H., 1914-1915; Tso, Hsueh-yen (Edith), 1926-1927, 1948, 1969; Tsurumi, 1922; Tuberculosis Sanitarium; 1925-1926, 1930, 1936 (Director; Greene; Gregg; Houghton; Korns; Mason; Resident Director; Tsur; Van Allen); Tuffier, T., 1921-1922
  Items of special note in this folder include a Subscription Book, from a letter from Van Allen to Greene (July 14, 1934), found under the mark-up Tuberculosis Sanitarium; and "RF and its Medical Institution in Peking" (1922), found under the mark-up Tuffier.
- Un, 1916, 1937, 1940 (Box 156, Folder 1134)
  Uniforms, 1937, 1940; Union Medical College, 1916 (McLean/Greene Report)
- United (B-N) (Box 156, Folder 1135)
  United Board for Christian Colleges in China, 1948-1950 (Cameron); United Clearing Board, 1944-1946; United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (UNRRA), 1944-1947 (Borcic; Bowen; Director; Ferguson; Forkner; Frye; Hunsey; Keefer; Kizer; Lambert; Loucks; Parker; Roots; Sachs; Tsur)